Logan Thomas

Senior Associate Data Scientist Born 1989 in Mountain View, CA



About me

I'm a highly motivated and naturally curious individual with 6 years of experience using data science & machine learning techniques. I exhibit an analytical and detail-oriented nature while placing strong value on building relationships.

Skills



Contact

6749 Catania Loop

✓ logan.thomas005@gmail.com

(321) 961-9107

in logan-thomas

loganthomas

Experience

Senior Associate Data Scientist I

Protection Engineering Consultants Austin, TX Aug 2019 - Present Advanced Technology & Research Team

Python Technical Curriculum Developer & Online Instructor

> DataCamp Remote Feb 2019 - Present

Lead Data Scientist

Nielsen Austin, TX Oct 2018 - Aug 2019 Machine Learning & Algorithms Team

Senior Data Scientist

Nielsen San Francisco, CA Aug 2016 - Oct 2018 **Digital Product Team**

Applied Analytics Program Associate - School of **Professional Studies**

Columbia University Remote Sep 2016 - Dec 2016 Applied Analytics in an Organizational Context

Data Scientist

Nielsen Tampa, FL & San Francisco, CA July 2014 - Aug 2016 **Emerging Leaders Program**

Education

University of Florida

Master of Science in Mechanical Engineering 2012 - 2014 Minor in Statistics

Palm Beach Atlantic University

Bachelor of Science in Mathematics 2008 - 2012 Minor in Biblical Studies; Graduated Summa Cum Laude

Projects

turkey-bowl repo-scrape python-practice **Pvthon Pvthon Pvthon** Thanksgiving tradition -GitHub metadata Collection of personal Mock NFL fantasy scraping (Hacktoberfest). Python notes, challenges, football draft. and scripts.



pint

pyjanitor deap Pythonic API for elegant **Distributed Evolutionary** Python package to define, data cleaning and method Algorithms in Python. operate and manipulate https://github.com/DEAP/ physical quantities - the